{
    "subject": "resource/Nachrichten",
    "predicate": "ontology/language",
    "object": "resource/German_language",
    "human_readable": "Nachrichten is written in German.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7903823852539062,
            "question": "What language is Nachrichten written in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5561402440071106,
            "question": "What type of information might be found in Nachrichten?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4722200036048889,
            "question": "Can you translate 'Nachrichten' into English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3990810215473175,
            "question": "Is Nachrichten a commonly used word in English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3546229302883148,
            "question": "Are there any regional variations in the use of 'Nachrichten'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22189539670944214,
            "question": "How has the internet changed the way Nachrichten is consumed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1676570177078247,
            "question": "What are some examples of words that sound similar to 'Nachrichten' in other languages?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07747279852628708,
            "question": "What are some popular German news sources?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04550634324550629,
            "question": "Are there any international news organizations that use German as their primary language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04184475168585777,
            "question": "What other languages besides German are commonly used for news reporting?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Nachrichten is written in German.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8526_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any international news organizations that use German as their primary language?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8526_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some popular German news sources?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8526_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some examples of words that sound similar to 'Nachrichten' in other languages?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8526_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8526_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8526_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8526_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8526_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8526_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8526_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8526_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8526_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8526_87.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8526_91.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format for your question:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple, as it mentions that \"Nachrichten\" (German) has a similar meaning to \"news\" (English), but are not really the same word with the same meanings. The documents also mention that Nachrichten is used for a certain type of radio or TV program, and can be either singular or plural depending on whether there is more than one."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe context information provided clearly indicates that \"Nachrichten\" is a word used in German, supporting the statement that it is written in German."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}